Guide to the American Planning Association records, 1925-2015.
American Planning Association records,
- University of Nebraska-Lincoln: Master of Community and Regional Planning (MCRP) Volume 1: Text, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- University of Nebraska-Lincoln: (MC) Vol. 2: Appendices, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- University of Kansas: Masters (MUP), 1983 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Clemson University: Masters (MCRP), 1983 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- University of California, Berkeley: Masters (MCRP), 1982 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- University of British Columbia: Masters of Art or Master of Science Planning, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Georgia Tech: Masters (MCP), 1982 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- University of Florida: Masters (MAURP), 1983 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- University of Eastern Washington: Batchelor (BAURP); Masters (MURP), 1983 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- University of Eastern Washington: Information & Requirements for MURP, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- University of Eastern Washington: MURP, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- University of Eastern Washington: BUP, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Alabama A & M: Master (MCP), 1981 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Cornell University: Master (MRP), 1981 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- University of Southern California: Master of Planning, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- University of Illinois, Urbana -Champaign: Bachelor of Arts and Urban Planning (BAUP); Master (MUP), 1982 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- University of Illinois, Urbana-Champ Bachelor of Arts and Urban Planning, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- University of Cincinnati: Bachelor (BUP), 1982 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- University of Cincinnati: Master (Ml), 1982 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- University of Cincinnati: Master (MCP), 1982 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- University of Wisconsin, Madison: Master; (MSURP), 1982 (Box 15, Folder 3-5)
- Virginia Commonwealth University: Master; (MURP), 1981 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Texas ASM University: Master (MUP), 1981 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Rutgers University: Master (MCRP), 1982 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Rutgers University course outlines, Dept of Urban Planning, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Portland State University: Master (MSP), Undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Virginia Tech: Master (MURP), 1978 (Box 15, Folder 11-12)
- Florida State University: Master (MSP), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- University of Pittsburgh: Master (MURP), 1978 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Alabama A & M: Master (MCP), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Alabama A & M: Master (MCP), 1981 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- New York University: Master (MUP), 1977 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Ohio State University (Vols. 1 & 2): Master (MCRP), 1983 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Ohio State University: Master (MCRP), 1983 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Pratt Institute (Part 1): Master (M£???, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Pratt Institute (Part 2) MSCRP, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Pratt Institute (Part 3) MSCRP, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- San Jose State University: Master (K,???, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- University of Puerto Rico, Rio Piedras: Master (MP), 1982 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- University of Texas, Arlington: Master (MCRP), 1982 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- University of Texas, Arlington: Master (MCRP), 1983 (Box 16, Folder 8-10)
- Missouri Chapter, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 1-3)
- New York State Office of Parks & Recreation: "Urban Parks", 1981 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Anne Squire, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Vicki Pflaumer, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Wisconsin/Illinois, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Montgomery County, Md. - Preservation of Agriculture & Rural Open Space, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 8-10)
- Portland, Oregon, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Colorado Chapter, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Oakland, Cal. - Rehab Right, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- San Francisco Bay Region - Environment & Resource Planning Study, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 14-15)
- San Francisco, Cal. - Endangered Harvest, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Sarasota County, Fla. - APOXSEE, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 17-18)
- Dane County, Wisconsin - Dane County Solid Waste Program, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Boston, Mass. - "West Broadway Comprehensive Renewal Program", 1983 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- APA Energy Planning Division, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- APA Transportation Planning Division, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- National Capital Area Chapter, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Oregon Chapter, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Marvin R. Springer, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Charles Kusic - Berkshire County, MA, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 26-28)
- Los Angeles, CA, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- APA Planning and Law Division, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 1-11)
- Utah Chapter, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Maryland Department of Natural Resources Environmental Law Institute, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- King County Annual Growth Reports, Washington, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Allan B. Jacobs, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Calvert County Comprehensive Plan, Md., 1985 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Withlacoochee Regional Hurricane Evacuation Program, Fla., 1985 (Box 19, Folder 17-24)
- Hardin County, Kentucky, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Utah Chapter - AICP, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- APA Utah Chapter - Planning Commissioner, Undated (Box 19, Folder 27)
- APA Utah Chapter - Program Notebook, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Cisneros/Target '90, San Antonio, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Mary Lou Henry - Diana Donald Award, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- California Chapter, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- Margaret Moorehead and Larry Epstein, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 32-33)
- Oregon Nevada Chapter, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 34)
- Arizona Chapter, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 35)
- Anchorage, Alaska, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 36-37)
- Miami, Fla. - Ocean Drive, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 38-39)
- Carol D. Barrett, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Marcy Benstock, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Jessie N. Butler, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Gushing Niles Dolbeare, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 4-6)
- Loveland Service Cost Recovery System, Colorado, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Margarita McCoy, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- City of Las Cruces, New Mexico, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Oregon Land Use Planning, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 10-12)
- The Arapahoe Greenway, Denver, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Virginia Certified Planning Commissioners' Program, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 14-15)
- The Virginia Tech Master Plan, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- "Sheltering the Homeless: A Profile Plan for Montgomery county, Ohio, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- The Women's Institute for Housing and Economic Development, Inc., 1987 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Suncoast Section Newsletter, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Lawrence Livingston, Jr., AICP, J.D., 1987 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Hamlets of the Adirondacks, NY, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Florida, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Pennsylvania Chapter, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- San Jose, California, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Colorado Chapter, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 25-26)
- Community for Creative Non-violence, Washington, D.C., Undated (Box 20, Folder 27-28)
- Vallejo, California - Alibi Clock/Bar Burke, Undated (Box 20, Folder 29)
- VIAH, Inc. (Visalians Interested In Affordable Housing), Visaliei, California, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Roanoke, Virginia, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Jacquelirie Leavitt, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Louis B. Wetmore, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Salisbury, Maryland - Rural Neighborhood Organization Project, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Newspaper Clippings(Photocopies), Undated (Box 20-21)
- City Governments, 1984-85 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- City Governments, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- City Governments, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- City Governments, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- City Governments, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- City Governments, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- City Governments, 1982-1985 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- City Governments, 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Discrimination in Housing, 1983-1985 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Environmental Problems, 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Environmental Problems, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Environmental Problems, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Funding for Housing, 1983-1985 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Gramm-Rudman Budget Plan, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Homeworker Employment, 1984-1986 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Jobs, Careers, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Land Use, 1984-1986 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Legal Problems, 1984-1987 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Migration Trends, Undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
- People in Planning, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 20-22)
- People in Planning, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 23-24)
- People in Planning, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- People in Planning, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 26-28)
- People in Planning, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Poverty Problems, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Preservation, 1983-87 (Box 21, Folder 31)
- Real Estate and Housing, 1983-84 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- Real Estate and Housing, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 33)
- Real Estate and Housing, 1986-87 (Box 21, Folder 34)
- Restoration, 1983-87 (Box 21, Folder 35)
- State Policies, 1983-85 (Box 21, Folder 36)
- State Policies, 1986-87 (Box 21, Folder 37)
- Tax Reform and Budget, 1983-85 (Box 21, Folder 38)
- Tax Reform and Budget, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 39)
- Transportation, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 40)
- Urban Development, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 41)
- Urban Development, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 42)
- Urban Development, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 43-44)
- Urban Development, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 45-46)
- Urban Development, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 47)
- Water Conservation, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 48)
- Policy Development Task Force, Leaders Letters, Sept. 1982-Jan. (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Leadership Letters (with Board minutes), 1983April -May 1983 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Performance, Planning, other Reports, Mar. -July 1983 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Drafts, corporate By Laws, Minutes of Meetings, Sept.-Dec. 1983 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Leadership Letters, Committee Reports, Jan. -Feb. 1984 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Draft reports, membership statistics, services to chapters, by-laws, Mar. 1984 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- By-laws, committee reports, jobs, Aug. -Oct. 1983 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Leadership letters, staff memos, minutes, Nov. 1974-Dec. 1984 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Programs, budgets, development plans, Jan. -April 1985 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Continuing education, leadership letters, advertising, May-Sept. 1985 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Continuing education, chapter presidents leadership letters, Dec. 1985 - June 1986 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- APA News, 1981-83 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- National Planning Conference, 1979-82 (Box 22, Folder 13-14)
- Zoning, 1983-84 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Zoning, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 16-24)
- Zoning, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 25-28)
- Carolina Planning, 1980-1985 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Examinations for Membership Qualification, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Dennis O'Harrow Biblio, 1952-1962 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Articles, position paper, strategic plan, 1935-1984 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- ASPO manual, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- News Bulletins, 1947,1949 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- News Bulletin, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- News Bulletin, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- American Institute of Certified Planners: directories, 1980, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- American Institute of Planners: handbook, special committee program, 1940, 1958, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- American Planning Association: directories, annual reports, 1980-1992 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Planners' organizations, directories: planning consultants, Arizona, Connecticut, Florida, Georgia, Indiana, Maryland, Michigan, New York City, North Carolina, Oregon, Utah, Virginia, 1976-1993 (Box 23, Folder 11-17)
- American Planning Association Planning & Law Division: directories, 1988-1991 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- American Planning Association Economic Development Division: directory, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- American Society of Planning Officials: Planning in Europe, 1935, 1937, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Local Capital Improvements and Development Management, HUD & NSF, June l980 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Habitat Protection Planning Where the Wild things Are APA, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Converting Storefronts to Housing APA, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Local Capital Improvements and Development: Executive Summary June 1980 APA, Report to the Toledo- Lucas County Plan Commissions on the Organization of the Planning Program, c.1979,1980 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Subdividing Rural America ASPO, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Preservation of historic districts ASPO, Planning for preservation ASPO, 1956, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- The Urban Planner in Health Planning ASPO, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Local Capital Improvements and Development ASPO, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- The Honolulu Study ASPO, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Greenville [South Carolina] ASPO, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Profiles of State Planning Associations in the United States, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Health Planning and the Environment: A Preventive Focus ASPO, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Guides for community planning ASPO, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- An Address "Plan Your City or Lose It" by Walter Blucher ASPO, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Organization and Administration of a City Planning Department, Zoning Changes and Variances, Urban Redevelopment Legislation in the United States ASPO, Statement of Real property, Municipal - Legislation: IUPC, Home Rule Charters (bibliography), 1935-1978 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Children and the city by Olga Adams ASPO, Action for Cities A guide for Community Planning: ASPO, Is Manhattan Beyond Hope? Citizens' Housing and Planning Council, 1952, 1943, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- The Atlanta Region Metropolitan Planning Commission The Years Ahead ASPO, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- Example of a Non-metropolitan Overall Program ASPO, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 38)
- Example of a City Overall Program Design ASPO (2 copies), 1972 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Profiles of State Planning Associations in the United States ASPO, 1970, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 2-3)
- An Administrative Study ASPO, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- AIP/ ASPO Merger
  - AIP/ ASPO Merger: A Report on a Possible Linkage Between AIP and ASPO, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 5-6)
  - AIP/ ASPO Merger: History of AIP/ ASPO Merger Attempts up to 1976 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - AIP/ ASPO Merger: Draft A Report On a Possible Linkage Between AIP and ASPO, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - AIP/ ASPO Merger: Survey, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - AIP/ ASPO Merger: Proposal for Formation of APA, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - AIP/ ASPO Merger: American Institute of Certified Planners Corporate Bylaws, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - AIP/ASPO Merger: Merger Committee, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - AIP/ ASPO Merger: Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - AIP/ASPO Merger: Miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - AIP/ASPO Merger: APA Financial Plan, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - AIP/ASPO Merger: APA Presidents' Round Table (transcription received 1985), Undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - AIP/ASPO Merger: Timetable of Key Events, Summary of the Plan to Consolidate AIP and ASPO into The American Planning Association, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - AIP/ASPO Merger: Summary of Plan to Consolidate ASPO and AIP into APA, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - AIP/ASPO Merger: Articles of Incorporation, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - AIP: Board of Governors - General Correspondence, 1935-1954, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 20-24)
  - AIP/ASPO Merger: Bylaws, summary, clippings, 1977-1979 (Box 24, Folder 25-27)
  - AIP/ASPO Merger: notes and correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 28-29)
  - AIP/ASPO Merger: committee reports, recommendations, personnel policies, financial statements, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 30-31)
- American City Planning Institute, Board of Governors, Business Meetings, 1935-1941 (Box 24, Folder 32-34)
- AIP Board of Governors and President: Founding and History, American City Planning, By-laws and Constitution History, By-laws, 1935-1964 (Box 24, Folder 35-39)
- AIP Registration and Licensure of Planners, 1956-1972 (Box 25, Folder 1-4)
- AIP Board of Governors minutes, 1963-1978 (Box 25, Folder 5-8)
- American Institute of Certified Planners: Board of Governors Meetings & Records (T.G. Rose), 1963-1977 (Box 25, Folder 9-11)
- AIP: Board of Governors minutes, 1956-1969 (Box 25, Folder 12-16)
- AIP: Board of Governors minutes, 1970-1976 (Box 25, Folder 17-19)
- AIP: Organization, Goals, Code; History of Membership; AIP Awards; Library-Archive Inventory, 1962-1978 (Box 25, Folder 20-22)
- AIP: Supplementary Records to Accompany the Official Record of the Minutes of the Board of Governors Mtgs., 1944-1954 (Box 25, Folder 23-25)
- AIP: Board of Governors Minutes, 1956-1969 (Box 25, Folder 26-28)
- AIP: Board of Governors Minutes, 1970-1976 (Box 25, Folder 29-31)
- AIP: Board of Governors Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 32-33)
- National Conferences on City Planning (17 bound volumes, 4 loose issues), 1909, 1911-1912,1942-1955 (Box 26)
- National Conferences on City Planning (14 bound volumes), 1940 (Box 27)
- National Conferences on City Planning (17 bound volumes), 1941-1955 (Box 28)
- Horizons and Imperatives: National Congress of Planning, Joint AIP/ ASPO National Planning Conference; AIP Annual Conference (audio tapes), 1976, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 1-10)
- Planning conference audio tapes, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 1-12)
- AIP News, 1950-1976 (Box 31, Folder 1-9)
- Journal of the American Institute of Planners, 1974-1978 (Box 31, Folder 10-14)
- Utah Chapter Newsletters, 1980-1984 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Wisconsin Chapter Newsletters, 1979-1983 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- National Capitol Area Chapter Newsletters, 1974-1977 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- National Capitol Area Chapter Newsletters, 1978-1980 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- California - San Diego Chapter Newsletters, 1978-1984 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- New England Chapter Newsletters, 1974-1984 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- New York Metro Chapter Newsletters, 1975-1984 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Central Pennsylvania Chapter Newsletters, 1978-1985 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Chapter Newsletters, 1974-1985 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Ohio Chapter Newsletters, 1973-1984 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- North Carolina Chapter Newsletters, 1982-1984 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- West Virginia Chapter Newsletters, 1980-1984 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Arizona Chapter Newsletters, 1971-1983 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Virginia Chapter Newsletters, 1978-1985 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- South Carolina Chapter Newsletters, 1973-1983 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Washington Chapter Newsletters, 1974-1983 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- North Carolina Chapter Newsletters, 1973-1981 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Texas Chapter Newsletters, 1975-1982 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Texas Chapter Newsletters, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- APA Testimonies and Statements to Congress and Government Agencies, 1981-1993 (Box 33)
- American Society of Planning Officials (ASPO) - Member Questionnaires and Survey, 1973 (Box 33)
- Correspondence on Termination of the APA Planning Education Division, 1982 (Box 33)
- APA Chapter Manual, 1983 (Box 33)
- APA - "Los Fundamentos de Planificacíon de Sitios" (Includes VHS tape), Undated (Box 33)
- APA Planning Official Survey, February 1993 (Box 33)
- American Institute of Planners (AIP) Proceedings of National Conferences, 1957,1959-1969 (Box 34, Folder 1-13)
- AIP Examination Readings, Undated (Box 34, Folder 14)
- American Society of Planning Officials (ASPO) Conferences on State Planning Administration, 1935-1936 (Box 34, Folder 15-16)
- Planners Journal (ASPO) [scattered issues], 1935-1940 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Private Planning for the Public Interest, Undated (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Plan for the Organization of the American Institute of Planners Resource Collection, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- American Society of Consulting Planners Directory of Firms, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- List of U.S. Natural Resources Planning Board publications, Undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous notes on publications, Undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Correspondence and drafts of summary of the plan to consolidate AIP and ASPO in to the American Planning Association, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- The Planning Department of the Maryland Special Capital Park and Planning Commission: Recommendations of the American Society of Planning Officials, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- American Institute of Certified Planners Roster, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Summary of Planning Policies of the American Planning Association, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- ASPO/ AIP joint publications: Colleges and Universities Offering Planning and Related Degree Programs, Education and Career Information for Planning and Related Fields; ASPO publications: ntis??? (3 issues including 1 on day care), The Neighborhood Technical Information Service Final Report, 1973-1975 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Planners Book Service Catalogs (2), 1998 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Planning (ASPO), 1957-1971 (Box 36, Folder 1-15)
- ASPO Index to Proceedings of National Planning Conferences, 1909-1961 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- ASPO Agenda for the New Urban Area, Undated (Box 36, Folder 17)
- ASPO Conference on Planning Problems, 1941 (Box 36, Folder 18)
- City Planning (v. 1 not bound, v. 2-9 bound), 1925-1934 (Box 37, Folder 1-10)
- American Planning and Civic Annual, 1943,1951-1956 (Box 37, Folder 11-17)
- AIP News, 1975,1976-1978 (Box 38)
- APA News, 1979-1983 (Box 38)
- Minority Fellowship Historical Materials, Undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Amps Foundation Solicitation, Undated (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Minority Fellowship program Ford Foundation Proposal, Undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
- APA Fellowship Issues, 1980's (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Technical Division Council Meetings, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Minutes of SRC Cincinnati, October 1980 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Divisions Council Meetings, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Minority Fellowships, ASPO, ASPO- AIP Joint Project, Pre-1981, 1976-77 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Division Council Meetings, Boston, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Divisions Council Meetings, Dallas, May 9,1982 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Divisions Council Meetings, Seattle, April 17, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Divisions Council Meetings, Twin Cities, May 5-9, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Divisions Council Meetings, Montreal, April 20, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Fellowship History, Undated (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Minority Recruitment - HUD-Schools, Undated (Box 39, Folder 15)
- AIP/ AMPS, Undated (Box 39, Folder 16)
- AIP-Minority Recruitment Film Proposal, April 1970 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- AIP/ ASPO Folder, Undated (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Community Energy Planning, Undated (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Community Energy Management Workshop and Gaming Simulation, Undated (Box 39, Folder 20)
- The City in the Year 2000 3rd Energy Planning Workshop (11) Energy Planning, Undated (Box 39, Folder 21)
- SRC Business Meeting, Chicago, IL, Spring 1993 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- SRC Minutes, Washington, D.C., Spring 1992 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- SRC Business Meeting Minutes, Charleston, SC, Fall 1991 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- SRC Business Minutes, New Orleans, LA, Undated (Box 39, Folder 25)
- SRC Minutes, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 26)
- Minutes SRC, Boston, April 26, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 27)
- Minutes of SRC Officers with APA Staff, Washington, Feb. 1991 (Box 39, Folder 28)
- SRC: Atlanta, GA; Los Angeles, CA Minutes and Conference Materials, 1986-1990 (Box 39, Folder 29)
- SRC: San Francisco, CA; Seattle, WA; Minneapolis, MN; Montreal, Que.; New York, NY; San Antonio, TX, 1980-1990 (Box 39, Folder 30)
- Annual Report - Alabama, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 31)
- Annual Report - Alaska, 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 32)
- Annual Report - Arizona, 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 33)
- Annual Report - Arkansas, 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 34)
- Annual Report - California, 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 35)
- Annual Report - Colorado, 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 36)
- Annual Report - Connecticut, 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 37)
- Annual Report - Delaware, 1981-1982 (Box 39, Folder 38)
- Annual Report - Florida, 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 39)
- Annual Report - Georgia, 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 40)
- Annual Report - Hawaii, 1981-1982 (Box 39, Folder 41)
- Annual Report - Illinois, 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 42)
- Annual Report - Indiana, 1983-1984 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Annual Report - Iowa, 1983-1984 (Box 40, Folder 2)